<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Football Club</string>

    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <array name="club_description">
        <item>FC Barcelona, also known simply as Barcelona and familiarly as Barça, is based in Barcelona, Catalonia,
            Spain. The team was founded in 1899 by a group of Swiss, English and Spanish footballers led by Joan Gamper.
            During the 20th century, \"Barça\" has become a Barcelona symbol, a symbol that represents the Catalan
            identity as a nation. That\'s why it is said that \"Barça\" is more than a Club.
        </item>
        <item>Real Madrid C.F. are a professional football club based in Madrid, Spain. In addition to their domestic
            success, Real Madrid\'s reputation as a major club was established by their outstanding record in the
            European Cup. To date, they have been crowned champions of Europe a record thirteen times.
        </item>
        <item>FC Bayern Munich is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria. It is best known for its professional
            football team, which plays in the Bundesliga, the top tier of the German football league system, and is the
            most successful club in German football history, having won a record 28 national titles and 18 national
            cups.
        </item>
        <item>Commonly known as City, is a football club in Manchester, England. Founded in 1880 as St. Mark\'s (West
            Gorton), it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894. The club\'s home
            ground is the City of Manchester Stadium in east Manchester, to which it moved in 2003, having played at
            Maine Road since 1923.
        </item>
        <item>Commonly known as Man. United or simply United, is a professional football club based in Old Trafford,
            Greater Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football.
            Nicknamed \"the Red Devils\", the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878, changed its name
            to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910.
        </item>
        <item>Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England, that competes in the Premier
            League. Founded in 1905, the club\'s home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge. Chelsea won the First
            Division title in 1955, followed by various cup competitions between 1965 and 1971. The past two decades
            have seen sustained success, with the club winning 23 trophies since 1997.
        </item>
        <item>Commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a professional football club in Milan, Italy,
            founded in 1899. The club has spent its entire history, with the exception of the 1980–81 and 1982–83
            seasons, in the top flight of Italian football, known as Serie A since 1929–30.
        </item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club was founded in 1886 as a munition workers\' team from Woolwich, then in Kent, now
            southeast London. They turned professional in 1891 and joined The Football League two years later. They were
            promoted to the First Division in 1904 but financial problems meant they were liquidated and reformed. They
            were bought out by Sir Henry Norris that year and to improve the club\'s financial standing, he moved the
            team to Arsenal Stadium, Highbury, north London in 1913.
        </item>
    </array>

</resources>
